https://www.gmt.co.in/privacy-policy/

Privacy policy | We protect your confidentiality and integrity of data
Skip to content
Search for:
CMM TRAINING PROGRAMME
WHY IS GMT CMM BEST SUITED FOR YOU?
Privacy Policy
Guindy Machine Tools Limited is committed to protecting all the information you share with us. We follow stringent procedures to help protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of data stored on our systems. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to perform their duties are allowed such access. Any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution.
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE.
YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS AND PERSONAL INFORMATION
Guindy Machine Tools Limited ask you for your name, phone number and email address. This information is necessary to send you a quote. We may also need your email address or phone numbers to contact you if we have questions about your enquiry. We may also use your email address to notify you about new services or special promotional programs, or send you information. At any time, you can notify us that you wish to stop receiving these emails.
SERVER LOGS
In an effort to make our Website as effective and enjoyable as possible, the computers that operate it collect information each time you visit. We store these statistics in server logs. Once again, these statistics do not identify you personally, but provide us information regarding the type of user who is accessing our Website and browsing activities of that user. This data may include: the IP address of the user accessing our Website (i.e. the unique I.D. number of the user’s computer), the type of browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.) and the operating system (Windows, Mac OS, etc.), the Website the user last visited before linking to our Website, how long the user accessed our Website in any given session, and the date and time of access. We may make extensive use of this data at an aggregated level in order to understand how our Website is being used. We may share some of the aggregate findings (not the specific data) with advertisers, sponsors, investors, strategic partners, and others in order to help grow our business.
PRIVACY POLICIES OF THIRD PARTY WEBSITES
This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other websites that may be accessible through this Website have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. If you link to any such website, we urge you to review the respective website’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.
CHANGES IN POLICY
We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy in the “Privacy Policy” section of the Website. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on the Website. It is the responsibility of each User to review the Website and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after the effectiveness of such revisions constitutes your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
Guindy Machine Tools Ltd, Chennai, India
CONTACT US CALL +91 87544 83577E-Mail: esales@gmt.co.in
QUICK LINKSCNC Lathe Chuck
Manual Chucks
Special Workholding
Surface Plates
Metrology Special Applications
Rotary Indexing Tables
GET IN TOUCHPhone+91 8754483577Address214, Velachery Tambaram Main Road,
